Welcome to Krishna Trading Tips 24.
Friends, today we are going to talk
about ICICI Low LMA General Insurance shares.
Friends, today its quarter 4 numbers are going to be
disclosed.
According to market sentiment, its results are
expected to be excellent.  If its results are
strong, then this stock can
see a tremendous rise.
Friends, if we talk about today, today this stock has
seen a rise of about 3.8%.
Currently the stock is trading at around ₹837.10.
If there is a jump in its revenue and net
profit, then the
stock may see a tremendous rise.
Come on friends, let us see
what its revenue and net profit is.
Friends, first of all let us talk about its sales,
in the September quarter, sales worth Rs 6869 crore were made.
Friends,
sales worth Rs 695 crore were made in the December quarter.  That means, friends, if we
look at it quarter on quarter and year on year, we are
seeing tremendous growth in its sales.  This
is a plus point for the company.  Friends, if we talk about its net
profit, a
net profit of Rs 820 crore was seen in the September quarter.
Friends, a
net profit of Rs 659 crore was seen in the December quarter.  That means,
friends, if we look at it quarter on quarter and year on
year, we are seeing a decline in it.
Friends, if we
talk about the reserves of the company, then it has very good
reserves of about Rs 15499 crore.
Friends, if we talk about borrowing, there is only zero
borrowing, which means that the company
is completely debt free.  It can make good profits in the coming time.
Friends, if we
talk about its share holding pattern, then the
promoter's holding in it
remained around 51% in the December quarter.
Friends, if we talk about the holding of FI in this, then it
remains around 21.5%.
Talking about DI's holding, it
remains around 1.5%.
Talking about the government, the government continues to hold a shareholding of 0.10%.
Talking about the public,
about 6.5% share holding
remains with the public.  Overall,
friends, its share holding pattern
looks absolutely positive.
Friends, if we look at the overall situation, the financial position of this company looks
very good.  It can
make good profits in the coming time.  Friends, there is
no buy or sell recommendation here.  The video is only for
educational purposes.  You can make an
investment strategy only with the advice of your financial advisor.